HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/005 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- J.E.B. Rochester, NY (Box 10, Folder 25)
- J.E.B. Sacramento (Box 10, Folder 26)
- J.E.B. San Diego, CA (Box 10, Folder 27)
- J.E.B. San Francisco, CA (Box 10, Folder 28)
- J.E.B. San Pedro, CA (Box 10, Folder 29)
- J.E.B. Scranton, PA (Box 10, Folder 30)
- J.E.B. Seattle, WA (Box 10, Folder 31)
- J.E.B. St. Louis, MO (Box 10, Folder 32)
- J.E.B. St. Paul, Minn. (Box 10, Folder 33)
- J.E.B. Syracuse, NY (Box 10, Folder 34)
- J.E.B. Vancouver, BC, Canada (Box 10, Folder 35)
- J.E.B. Washington, DC (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Journal Math Class (Box 10, Folder 37)
  53 photographs
- Juliano Senate - Testimony - Meal Tax - Deduction - 5/1993 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Justice for Janitors - DC Protest (Box 10, Folder 39)
- King Memorial March August 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  33 photographs; proof sheets
- Kitchens (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Kitchens (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Korean Visitor (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Labor of love concert (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Ladies Lunch 7/8/1996 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  50 photographs
- Ladies Lunch 7/8/1996 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Landmark monuments (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Landscapes (Box 10, Folder 48)
  2 photographs; 22 slides
- Larry's Bar and Grill (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Las Vegas Misc. 1999 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Las Vegas Photos (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Las Vegas Post cards (Box 10, Folder 52)
  3 post cards
- Las Vegas -- Victory Rally and Kirkland Rally, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  proof sheets; negatives
- Leafleting (Box 10, Folder 54)
- MADD Press Conference 1984 - 21 drinking age (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Malaysian visitors -- October 1989 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- March on Washington -- 1993 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Mamott International Campaign (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Medicare Act (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Meeting (unidentified) (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Meeting (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Meeting -- Ron Richardson (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Meeting - Staff Representatives -- 2/16/1992 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  72 photographs
- Meeting -- DC -- 11/1992 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Members at work (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Members at work -- 1996 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Members at work. May 1996 Capitol Hilton and Sheraton (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Members Board meeting (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Miami Beach (Box 10, Folder 76)
  91 photographs
- Midwest Organizing Seminar (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Midwest Organizing Seminar (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 1)
  49 photographs
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 2)
  proof sheets; 29 photographs
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 3)
  26 photographs; 1 floppy disc
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Contact Sheets (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Photocopies (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 11, Folder 8)
  29 photographs
- Miscellaneous Photographs (captioned) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  28 photos
- Miscellaneous Photographs of Photos (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Montreal Office Shots - October 24, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Motels (Box 11, Folder 12)
- NAACP Show (Box 11, Folder 13)
- NAACP Show 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- NAACP Show -- 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- NAACP Show 1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- National Coordinating Committee (Box 11, Folder 17)
- National Fire Protection Association (Box 11, Folder 18)
  5 slides
- National Park Service (Box 11, Folder 19)
- National Press Club (Box 11, Folder 20)
- New Otani Campaign, LA 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- New York World Fair (Box 11, Folder 22)
- O'Garas' 40th Anniversary -- 11/18/1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Office - Unidentified Negatives (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Offices (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Office Staff (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Office Staff (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Office Staff - (Box 11, Folder 28)
  Contact sheets
- Office Staff (negatives) (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Office Staff (negatives) (Box 11, Folder 30)
- 1996 Officers' Report Photographs (Box 11, Folder 31)
  51 photographs; 49 slides
- 1996 Officers' Report Photographs (Box 11, Folder 32)
  183 photographs
- 1996 Officers' Report Photographs (Box 11, Folder 33)
  30 photographs; contact sheets
- Old Photographs (1800's) (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Old Photographs - Early 1900's (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Operation Footlight (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Organizers -- 1959 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Organizing (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Organizing Seminars -- 1983 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Organization Team -- 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Other Unions (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Outdoor Activities (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Outdoor Activities (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Outdoor Activities -- 1993 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Outdoor Activities -- BBQ (Box 11, Folder 45)
  25 Photographs
- Outdoor Activities - Fishing (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Outdoor Activities - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 47)
  4 photographs; 1 slide
- Party Dept. (Box 11, Folder 48)
- People (Box 11, Folder 49)
- People (Box 11, Folder 50)
  69 photographs; 4 slides
- Photographs and Artwork (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Photos of text (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Plaque (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Portraits, Unidentified (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Puerto Rico - July 1991 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Puerto Rico Races (Box 11, Folder 56)
- PSS District Council (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Rallies Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Rallies - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Reception - Father Joseph Bernadine - Sept/Oct 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Restaurants (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Retirement Party - Brother Martinotter (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Sam and Harry's Dec. 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Sambos Boycott (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Sam Diego R-T-W Rally 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Saudi Santas (Dec. 1990) (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Secretaries (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Seminar (Box 12, Folder 11)
  99 photographs
- Seminar (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Seminar (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Seminar (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Seminar (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Seminar and ironworkers' support (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Senator Anoye and Paul Blake (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Senior Citizens (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Severance Pay (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Sky Chefs (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Sky Chefs (Box 12, Folder 21)
  19 photographs; 2 floppy discs
- Sky Chef Negotiators (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Social Security (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Solidarity Day (Box 12, Folder 24)
  14 photographs; 1 slide
- Solidarity Day, Balloon, Times Square, Sign on Building (Box 12, Folder 25)
  13 photographs; 8 slides
- Solidarity Day - Sept. 19 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  3 photographs; 17 slides
- Solidarity Day 1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Solidarity Day 1991 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Solidarity Day 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Solidarity Night (Box 12, Folder 30)
- South African Labor Leaders - Jan. 1995 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Speakers (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Speakers - Martin Luther King (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Sunnyville (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Delegations and Speakers (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Staff Photographs -- 1991 Office (Box 12, Folder 36)
  123 photographs
- Staff Photographs -- 1991 Office (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Staff 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  22 slides
- Staff - June 1996 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  10 slides
- Alaska Alliance - State Council (Box 12, Folder 40)
- California State Council (Box 12, Folder 41)
- California - State Council (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Massachusetts - State Council (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Minnesota - State Council (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Montana State Council (Box 12, Folder 45)
- New York State Council (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Pennsylvania State Council (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Washington State Council (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Strikes - Box Tree Strike (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Strikes - InterParking Strike -- 11/16/1999 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Strikes - Jefferson Strike (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Strikes - Kinney Systems Strike (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Strikes - Lake Tahoe Strike (Box 12, Folder 53)
  16 slides
- Strikes - Las Vegas Hotels Misc. (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Strikes - Las Vegas Strike 1984 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  37 photographs
- Las Vegas Strike (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Loews Hotel Strike (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Mark Hopkins Strike (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Marriot Strike (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Rainbow Room Strike (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Normandy Motor Inn (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Strikes and Marches Misc. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Oliver Carr (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Olivercare Strike (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Olivercare Strike (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Omni Hotel Strike (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Strikes - President Casino (Box 13, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Strike (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Sgros (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Strike Stork Club (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Strike, Wally's Turtle (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Thurmout - Sous Chef (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Unidentified event (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Union House, Union Bar (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Union Industries Show 1956 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Union Industries - Detroit's Cobb Hall (April, 1961) (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Union Industries Show 1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Union Industries Show - Philadelphia, PA 1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Union Industries Show 1968 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  32 photographs; 2 slides
- Union Industries Show 1969 -- Denver (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Union Industries Show -- 1970 -- New Orleans, LA (See July 1970 CIE) (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Union Industries Show 1971 -- Atlanta, GA (Box 13, Folder 28)
  Magazine clippings
- Union Industries Show 1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Union Industries Show -- Milwaukee, WI 1975 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  51 photographs
- Union Industries 1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  13 photographs; 35 slides
- Photos - 1976 U-1 Show (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Union Industries 1977 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  16 photographs; 24 slides
- Unlabeled (Union Industry 1978?) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  10 photographs; 36 slides
- Union Industries 1979 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  19 photographs; 13 slides
- Union Industries Show 1980 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Union Industries 1982 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Union Industries Show -- Pittsburgh -- 1982 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- U-I Show -- 1982 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- U-I Show 1982 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- U-I Show 1984 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- U-I Show 1984 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- U-I Show 1984 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- U-I Show 1984 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- U-I Show Sept. 1986 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- U-I Show 1987 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Union Industries Show 1990 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Union Industries Show 1991 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Canadian Union industries Shows (Box 13, Folder 49)
- UI Shows - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Union label (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Union Label Show - June 1960 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Union Label Week Aug. 1961 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- W and W Race (Box 14, Folder 1)
  95 photographs
- W and W Race (Box 14, Folder 2)
- V-S Hours and W and W Races -- SC-St. Louis (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 1974 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 1975 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 1976 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 1977 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 1977 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 1978 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 9)
- 1978 Waiters and Waitresses Race - Monterey, CA (Box 14, Folder 10)
- 1978 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 11)
- 1979 Waiters and Waitresses Race - Chicago (Box 14, Folder 12)
- 1979 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 1980 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 14)
- 1980 Waiters and Waitresses Race - New York (Box 14, Folder 15)
- 1981 Waiters and Waitresses Race -- Puerto Rico (Box 14, Folder 16)
  42 photographs; 16 slides
- 1982 Waiters and Waitresses Race (Box 14, Folder 17)
- W and W Race 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  46 slides
- W and W Race 1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- W and W Race 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Waiter and Waitresses Race -- St. Louis, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  2 photographs; 64 slides
- Waiters and Waitresses Race - St. Louis (Box 14, Folder 22)
  23 photographs; 76 slides
- Waiters and Waitresses Race (Miscellaneous) (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Waiters and Waitresses (Mixed) (Box 14, Folder 24)
- W and W Race (Slides) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  79 slides
- Washington Hilton (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Washington Hilton (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Washington Hilton (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Western Regional Conference (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Western Regional Office (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Williamsburg Rally, Local 32 -- C-4905 (1-6) 1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Workshop (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Workshop (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Workshops (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Workshops (Ruffin, Juliano, Arnodo) Delegations? (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Workshops - Staff -- O'Neill, Grella? (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Yale Strike (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Yes to the Union (Individuals) (Box 14, Folder 38)
- CIE - January/February 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  5 photographs; cartoon
- CIE - January /February 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- CIE - May/June 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- CIE -- July/August 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- CIE -- January/February 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  4 photographs; advertisements
- CIE -- November/December 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- CIE -- April 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- CIE -- Bill Clinton (Box 15, Folder 8)
  1 floppy disc; 1 photograph; advertisement
- CIE - Misc. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  8 photographs; newspaper articles
- CIE -- Misc. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  16 photographs; cartoons
- CIE -- Misc. (Box 15, Folder 11)
- CIE -- Misc. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Strikes (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Waiters and Waitresses Race 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Local 355 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Hanely, Edward (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Green, Lester (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Angelino, Anthony (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Anselmo, Anthony (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Arnold (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Belardi, Joseph (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Bilandic, Michael (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Boardman (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Bonar, Ron (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Brady, Dr. Preston (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Bramlet, Al (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Brown, J.W. (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Burke (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Callahan, "Mushy" (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Canty (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Cariola, Samuel F. (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Carlson, Carol (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Carroll, John A. (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Carter, Jimmy (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Casey, John A. (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Chiesa, Sherri (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Cicarddini, Joseph (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Clair, Joseph A. (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Clinton, William (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Cole, Gordon (ILPA) (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Conolly (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Coughlan, Pat (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Crenshaw, Ben (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Cullerton (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Daley (Jr.) (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Daly, Mayor R. (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Diaz, Ernesto (Box 16, Folder 29)
  7 slides; 8 photographs
- Diefenbach, Robert L. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  132 photographs
- Donovan, George (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Doppelt, Hyman B. (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Dougherty, Art (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Dougherty, Bill (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Dropkin, Morris (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Dufour, Angust (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Dufour, Gus (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Durazo (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Dykstra, Lynn (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Dyson, James (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Eatchel (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Elliott, Walter (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Ernst, Hugo (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Ernst, Hugo (Funeral) (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Ervolino, Francis (Box 16, Folder 45)
  newspaper clippings
- Esper, Anne (Box 16, Folder 46)
  8 slides
- Fabricus, John A (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Farr, Florence (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Feder, Jerry (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Felix, Fred (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Feller, Karl (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Franklin, Earl P. (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Furay, Mort (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Gamberg, Robert (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Garcia, Joe (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Garmatz, Rep. Edward A. (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Garogiola, Joe (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Gatson, Ramat (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Gavel, Mike (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Gazan, Max (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Georgine (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Gerardy, Jerry (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Getter, Ben (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Gibson, John (Box 16, Folder 64)
  10 photographs; newspaper articles
- Gilligan, John (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Gleason, Joe (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Goetz, Fred (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Gohg?, Walter (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Gonzales, Al (Box 16, Folder 70)
  6 photographs; 11 slides
- Govoni, Lou (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Green, Lester (Box 16, Folder 72)
  18 slides; 19 photographs
- Green, William (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Greenwood, Paul (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Grogan (Box 16, Folder 75)
- Hacker, Carl (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Hammer (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Hanley, Edward (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Hanely, Edward Jr. (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Hanley, Edward Jr. (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Hanely, Thomas (Box 16, Folder 80)
- Hansen, Thomas (Box 16, Folder 81)
  15 photographs; 6 slides
- Hardy, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 82)
- Harriman, Averell (Box 16, Folder 83)
- Harrison, George (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Henty, Colleen (Box 16, Folder 85)
  1 floppy; 48 photographs
- Herman, Dave (Box 16, Folder 86)
- Hernandez, Valentin (Box 16, Folder 87)
- Hilyer, Rhonda (Box 16, Folder 88)
  3 photographs; 4 slides
- Holohan, Gustava (Box 16, Folder 89)
- Hoyes, Woody (Box 16, Folder 90)
- Hussey, Frances (Box 16, Folder 91)
- Horne, W.E. (Box 16, Folder 92)
- Howard, R.C. (Box 16, Folder 93)
- Humphrey, Sen. Hubert (Box 16, Folder 94)
  7 photographs; newspaper clipping
- Jackson, Jesse (Box 16, Folder 95)
  77 photographs
- Jacobs, Viola (Box 16, Folder 96)
- Javits, Sen. (Box 16, Folder 97)
- Jodin, Claude (Box 16, Folder 98)
- Johnstone, A.R. (Box 16, Folder 99)
- Juliano, Bob (Box 16, Folder 100)
  24 photographs; 8 slides
- Kearney, John J. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Keenan, Joe (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Kennedy, Ted (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Kenneally, Jack (Box 17, Folder 4)
  13 photographs; 1 slide
- Kenney, John J (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Kenney, Marcel (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Kensinger, Harold (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Kinkade, Betty (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Kircher, Bill (Box 17, Folder 9)
  12 photographs; 1 slide
- Knox, Charles (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Koenig, Lou (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Kolling, Joe (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Kruschank, Nelson (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Landers, Candace (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Lane, Gertrude (Box 17, Folder 15)
  1 photograph; newspaper clipping
- Latham, James T. (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Lavin (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Leader, George M. (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Leckie, Sal (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Lee, William (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Lewis, Joe (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Lightford, J.T. (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Loughlin, James P. (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Lovitt, Moses (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Leavitt, Herman (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Luebert, Tim (Box 17, Folder 26)
- MacLeod, (Nick) (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Mahoney, Loretta (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Maloney (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Maloney, F.J. (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Mandela, Nelson (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Massimino, Joe (Box 17, Folder 32)
- McCastland, Paul (Box 17, Folder 33)
- McDevitt, James (Box 17, Folder 34)
- McDonough, C.T. (Box 17, Folder 35)
  22 photographs; newspaper clippings
- McHugh, Jerry (Box 17, Folder 36)
- McNamara, Pat (Box 17, Folder 37)
- McVey, Howard (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Meany, George (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Metz, Ferdinand (CIA President) (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Miller, Edward S. (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Miller, Edward S. (Danny Thomas Dinner) 1959, St. Louis, MO (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Miller leaving for ILO (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Miller, Edward S. (Testimonial Dinner) June 14, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Miller, Edward S. Youth Center (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Miller, Mrs. Edward S. (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Moe, Althea (Box 17, Folder 47)
  4 Photographs
- Monroe, Ernest (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Morgan, A.E. (Box 17, Folder 49)
  3 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Morris, Gladys (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Morty (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Muellenburg (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Mureo, Gus (Org.) (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Musial, Stan (Box 17, Folder 54)
- O'Brien, Hazel (Box 17, Folder 55)
- O'Gara, John (Box 17, Folder 56)
  20 photographs; 8 slides
- O'Hara, Jimmy (Box 17, Folder 57)
- O'Neill, Tip (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Packwood, Bob (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Papageorge, Stephen (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Paradise, Charlotte and Jay (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Parsumi, Henry (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Paulsen, Charles (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Paulsen, Ken (Box 17, Folder 64)
  27 photographs; 8 slides
- Peterson, Esther (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Petri, Nick (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Pitta, Vito (Box 17, Folder 67)
  24 photographs; 7 slides
- Pollard, William (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Polock, Bob (Box 17, Folder 69)
  2 photographs; newspaper article
- Posthauer, John J. (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Press, Julius (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Rao, Robert (Box 17, Folder 72)
  8 slides; 1 photograph
- Rasser, Fred H. (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Reid, Harry (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Reuther, Walter (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Reynolds, Jack (Box 17, Folder 76)
  2 photographs; newspaper clipping; 7 slides
- Richardson, F.C. (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Richardson, H. (Box 17, Folder 78)
- Richardson, Ron (Box 17, Folder 79)
  55 photographs; 4 slides
- Riggio, Frank (Box 17, Folder 80)
- Roberts, W.A. (Box 17, Folder 81)
- Rodriguez, Joe (Box 17, Folder 82)
- Rogan, Tom (Box 17, Folder 83)
- Ross, Bert (Box 17, Folder 84)
  11 photographs; newspaper articles
- Ross, Nancy (Box 17, Folder 85)
- Rourke, Joe (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Rovner, Ed (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Roxie (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Rubin, Joy (Box 17, Folder 89)
  4 photographs; newspaper clippings
- Russell, Arthur (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Rykunyk, Jaye (Box 17, Folder 91)
- Sands, Chas. E. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Sargent, John M. (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Schiffman, (Pinky) Herbert (Box 18, Folder 3)
  38 photographs; 3 slides
- Schnitzer, William (Box 18, Folder 4)
  17 photographs; newspaper clipping
- Scott, Harry (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Seitel, Nelson (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Showers, Lorena (Box 18, Folder 7)
  3 photographers
- Siegel, David (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Silverstein, Abe (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Sirabella, Vincent (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Smith, Richard (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Soderstrom, Rube (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Spano, Joseph (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Spanos, Tony (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Specht, Al (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Spencer, Dorothy (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Spilos, Steve (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Stamos, James (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Stefani, J. (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Stevens, James T. (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Stoltz, Lawrence (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Stormer, Dale (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Stormer, Ron (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Sullivan, Lenore K. (St. Louis, MO rep) (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Susi, A. (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Sweeney (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Sweet, Eldred and Fred (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Sweet, Gertrude (Box 18, Folder 28)
  69 photographs
- Tamarin, Henry (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Taylor, D. (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Totzke, Harvey (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Townsend, Jack (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Triplett, Herb (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Valley, Phil (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Van Arsdale, Harry (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Walker (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Ward, Peter (Box 18, Folder 37)
  2 photographs, 16 slides
- Weinberger, Jack (1) (Box 18, Folder 38)
  104 photographs
- Weinberger, Jack (2) (Box 18, Folder 39)
  wooden stamp; 51 photographs
- Weinberger, Mrs. (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Weston, Leyton (Box 18, Folder 41)
- White, Herschel (Box 18, Folder 42)
- White, Jack (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Wilhelm, John (Box 18, Folder 44)
  49 photographs 5 slides
- Williams, Sen. Harrison A. Jr. (Dem. NJ) (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Wolf, Julius (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Wolfgang, Myra (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Worhany (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Woswang, Nick (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Yelstein, Bons (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Yorty, Sam (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Zack, Rudolph (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Zambri, Onofrio (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Zucca, E. Zarni (Box 18, Folder 54)